fictiv.com 2015-03-19

# Fictiv | Privacy Policy

## FICTIV INC. PRIVACY POLICY

#### Last Updated: November 18th, 2013

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you (individuals and entities with printing needs and printers) is collected, used and disclosed by Fictiv, Inc. (“ **Fictiv** ”). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our website and other online services (collectively, the “Services”) or when you otherwise interact with us. 

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. 

### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

#### Information You Provide to Us

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you submit a design or become a Fictiv printer or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, fax number, credit card information and any other information you choose to provide. 

#### Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including: 

  * **Log Information:** We log information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Services. 
  * **Device Information:** We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information. 
  * **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:** We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us to improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular and count visits. We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below. 

#### Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including but not limited to identity verification services and credit bureaus. 

### USE OF INFORMATION

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to: 

  * Provide, maintain and improve our Services; 
  * Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and invoices, 
  * Communicate with you about products and services; 
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services; and 
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected. 

Fictiv is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries. 

### SHARING OF INFORMATION

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy: 

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf; 
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation; 
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Fictiv or others; 
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and 
  * With your consent or at your direction, including if we notify you through our Services that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information. 

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you. 

### SECURITY

Fictiv takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. 

#### YOUR CHOICES

#### Account Information

You may update, correct or delete information about you at any time by logging into your online account, emailing us at team@fictiv.com. If you wish to delete or deactivate your account, please email us at team@fictiv.com, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time. 

#### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services. 

#### Marketing and Promotional Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Fictiv by following the instructions in those emails or by Emailing team@fictiv.com and requesting to be removed from our mailing list. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations. 

#### CONTACT US

If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us at: team@fictiv.com, 415-580-2509. 

### NICE! YOU'RE ON THE WAITLIST

Want priority access? Checkout the email we just sent you—it has instructions on how to move up the line. In the meantime, visit our resource center to learn more about 3D printing.
